ILGWU Research Department Records 5780/168
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Management Labor Textile Advisory Committee, 1961-1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 51: Minutes of Meeting of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Held October 23, 1962, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 52: Minutes of Meeting of the Management of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Held January 8, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 53: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting Held February 28, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 54: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting Held March 28, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Management Labor Textile Advisory Committee, 1963-1965; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: List of Countries/Categories Under Restraint During the Long Term Arrangement, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Memorandum, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    By James S. Love, Jr. March 20, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Minutes of Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting Held May 15, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Minutes of Mangement-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held June 27, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Minutes of Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held July 31, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Minutes of Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held August 26, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Minutes of Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held October 1, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Minutes of Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held November 7, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Minutes of Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held November 7, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Minutes of Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held December 17, 1963, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held January 21, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held February 27, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held April 9, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held May 5, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held June 2, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee - Held July 7, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held August 4, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held September 1, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting- Held October 6, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held November 5, 1964, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held January 5, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held February 2, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held March 9, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held April 6, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held May 4, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Management Labor Textile Advisory Committee, 1965-1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held June 1, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Minutes of MLTAC and ITAC Meeting On July 13, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held July 13, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held August 3, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting Held September 9, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held October 5, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting Held November 9, 1965, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held January 13, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held February 8, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held March 8, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held April 5, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held May 10, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held June 7, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held July 6, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - held August 2, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 16: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held September 8, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 17: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting Held October 13, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 18: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held November 9, 1966, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held on January 5, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 20: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held February 1, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Item 21: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held March 7, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Management Labor Textile Advisory Committee, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held April 12, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Minutes of the Management Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held May 10, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Minutes of the Management Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held June 7, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held July 12, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: Prelimiary Memorandum -- Performance of the United States Textile and Apparel Industries in 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
    By Stanley Nehmer. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting Held August 8, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting Held September 6, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held October 3, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: Minutes of the Management-Labor Textile Advisory Committee Meeting - Held November 8, 1967, Publication (Box 4, Folder 12)
- U.S. Department of Commerce Industry & Trade Administration, Characteristics of the Apparel Industry, 1978; Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
  June 1978
  - Item 1: Characteristics of the Apparel Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 13)
    By Edward Gottfried. June 1978. Item is in English.
- Office of National Recovery Administration, Division of Review, Work Materials, No. 33, The Basic Code, 1936; Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
  February 1936
  - Item 1: Work Materials, No. 33. The Basic Code (Administrative Order No. X-61), Publication (Box 4, Folder 14)
    By W.H. Edmonds and W.W. Swift. February 1936. Item is in English.
- United States Department of Labor Wage and Hour Division, Knitted & Men's Woven Underwear & Commercial Knitting Industry, 1941; Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
  June 1941
  - Item 1: Knitted and Men's Woven Underwear And Commercial Knitting Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 15)
    June, 1941. Item is in English.
- United States Department of Labor, Wage & Hour Division, Transferability of Skill in the Apparel Industry, 1941; Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
  March 1941
  - Item 1: Transferability of Skill In the Apparel Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 16)
    March 1941. Item is in English.
- Office of National Recovery Administration, Division of Review, Wage & Hours in American Industry NRA Source Material, Labor Studies Section, 1936; Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
  March 1936
  - Item 1: Wages and Hours in American Industry NRA Source Material, Publication (Box 4, Folder 17)
    By Solomon Barkin, Anne Page. March 1936. Item is in English.
- Office of National Recovery Administration, Division of Review, Some Aspects of Women's Apparel Industry, Industries Studies Section, 1936; Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Some Aspects of the Women's Apparel Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 18)
    By Sherman Trowbridge. March 1936. Item is in English.
- United States Tariff Commission, Questionnaire Relating to TSUS Item 807.00, 1970; Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
  March 31, 1970
  - Item 1: United States Tariff Commission: Questionnaire Relating to TSUS Item 807.00, Publication (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Bureau of International Commerce, American Republics Division, Statement of Rates of Import Duties, 1969; Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
  August 27, 1969
  - Item 1: Statement of Rates On Import Duties, Publication (Box 4, Folder 20)
- University of Chicago Graduate School of Business, Survey of the Characteristics of National & International Union Leaders, 1960-1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Social Security Ignorance - It Can Cost You Money, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Julius Berman. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Survey of the Characteristics of National and International Union Leadership, Publication (Box 4, Folder 21)
    By Abraham Friedman, Joel Seidman. Item is in English.
- Teper, Lazare. Articles by Lazare Teper in International Free Trades Union News, 1948; Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
  June 1948
  - Item 1: International Free Trade Union News, Publication (Box 4, Folder 22)
    June 1948. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Memoranda Submitted by the I.L.G.W.U. to the Federal Security Agency Appeals Council on Behalf of Claimants, 1946; Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Memoranda: Submitted by the I.L.G.W.U. to the Federal Security Agency Appeals Council on Behalf of Claimants, Publication (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Federal Reserve Bank of New York, The Working Population of New York City, 1943; Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
  December 29, 1943
  - Item 1: The Working Population of New York City, Publication (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Teper, Lazare. Employment Stabilization, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
  September 26, 1963
  - Item 1: Employment Stabilization, Publication (Box 4, Folder 25)
    By Lazare Teper. September 26, 1946. Item is in English.
- Franz S. Leichter, A Return of the Sweatshop: A Call for State Action, 1979; Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Return of the Sweatshop: A Call for State Action, Publication (Box 4, Folder 26)
    By Franz S. Leichter. October 1979. Item is in English.
- Herberg, Will. The Old-Timers & the Newcomers, 1953; Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: The old-timers and the newcomers, Publication (Box 4, Folder 27)
    By Herberg, Will. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Statement of Lazare TeperBefore the Wage Stabilization Board, 1952; Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
  May 28, 1952
  - Item 1: Statement of Lazare Teperbefore the Wage Stabilization Board, Publication (Box 4, Folder 28)
    May 28, 1952. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Financial Analysis of Textron Inc. and Feinzig, Leonard. An Analytical Study of Textron Inc., 1946; Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Financial Analysis of Textron, Inc., Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Item 2: An Analytical Study of Textron, Incorporated, Publication (Box 4, Folder 29)
    By Leonard Feinzig. Item is in English.
- National Knitted Outerwear Association, The Contract System of Production of Infants' and Childrens' Knitted Outerwear Under the NRA, 1938; Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
  November 1, 1938
  - Item 1: The Contract System of Production of Infants' and Children's Knitted Outerwear Under the NRA, Publication (Box 4, Folder 30)
    By Harold R. Lhowe and Sidney S. Korzenik. November 1, 1938. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Eastern Isle Corporation Investigation and Report, 1939; Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Eastern Isle Corporation: Investigation and Report, 1939, Publication (Box 4, Folder 31)
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Eastern Isle Corporation Investigation & Report, Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Eastern Isle Corporation Investigation and Report, Publication (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Teper, Lazare. What is an Executive Worth?, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: What is an executive worth?, Publication (Box 4, Folder 33)
    By Lazare Teper. 1949. Item is in English.
- Labor Bureau, Inc. Time Studies of Dresses Up to and Including $3.75, 1934; Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Time Studies of Dresses Up To and Including $3.75, Publication (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Morris, Sherwood. Causes of Failure in the Textile Industry, 1933; Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Causes of Failure in the Textile Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 35)
    By Morris, Sherwood and May. Item is in English.
- Starr, Mark. People Must Speak to People, 1952; Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
  June 1952
  - Item 1: People must speak to people, Publication (Box 4, Folder 36)
    By Starr, Mark. Item is in English.
- Nagler, Isidore. Analysis of the Problems of the Women's Coat & Suit Industry, 1954; Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
  March 10, 1954
  - Item 1: Analysis of the Problems of the Women's Coat and Suit Industry and Suggested Recommendations for Their Solution, Publication (Box 4, Folder 37)
    By Isidore Nagler. March 10, 1954. Item is in English.
- Join Board of Sanitary Control, Seating and Posture, 1923; Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Seating and Posture, Publication (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Joint Board of Sanitary Control, Light & Illumination in Garment Shops, 1918; Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Light and Illumination in Garment Shops, Publication (Box 4, Folder 39)
- United Labor Policy Committee, Statement of the United Labor Policy Committee to the National Wage Stabilization Board, 1951; Publication (Box 4, Folder 40)
  January 11, 1951
  - Item 1: Statement of the United Labor Policy Committee to the National Wage Stabilization Board At Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 4, Folder 40)
    January 11, 1951. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Statement Submitted by I.L.G.W.U., A.F.L. to New Jersey State Commission on Post War Economic Welfare on Proposed Cash Sickness Benefit Plan, 1946; Publication (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Statement Submitted By International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, AFL to New Jersey State Commission On Post War Economic Welfare on Proposed Cash Sickness Benefits Plan, Publication (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Isserman & Kapelsohn, Cash Sickness Benefits, 1948; Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
  March 1948
  - Item 1: Cash Sickness Benefits, Publication (Box 4, Folder 42)
    By Isserman and Kapelsohn. March 1948. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, New Jersey Temporary Disability Benefits Law, Publication (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: New Jersey Temporary Disability Benefits Labor, Publication (Box 4, Folder 43)
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Statement for Hearing on October 18, 1948i.e. Temporary Disability Benefits Law & Proposed Amendments to the Temporary Disability Benefits Submitted by Commissioner Vincent J. Murphy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: 1. Statementfor hearingon October 18, 1948re Temporary Disability Benefits Law and 2. Proposed amendmentsto the Temporary Disability Benefits Law submitted by Commissioner Vincent J. Murphy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 44)
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Summary of the New York Temporary Disability Benefits Law, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Summary of the New York Temporary Disability Benefits Law, Publication (Box 4, Folder 45)
- I.L.G.W.U. Memorandum on Behalf of the I.L.G.W.U. at the Public Hearing on New Proposed Regulations under the New York Disability Benefits Law, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
  October 20, 1949
  - Item 1: Memorandum on Behalf of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 4, Folder 46)
    By Morris P. Glushien. October 29, 1949. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Assistant Executive Secretary, Statement Presented to the New York State Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial & Labor Conditions, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 47)
  December 5, 1950
  - Item 1: Statement of Behalf of the International Ladies' Gament Workers' Union, Publication (Box 4, Folder 47)
    By James Lipsig. December 5, 1950. Item is in English.
- Teper, Lazare. Statement Before the National Commission on Employment and Unemployment Statistics, 1978; Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
  July 26, 1978
  - Item 1: Statement before the National Commission on Employment and Unemployment Statistics, Publication (Box 4, Folder 48)
    By Teper, Lazare. July 26, 1978. Item is in English.
- Committee for "Slack" Investigation Report, 1942; Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
  November 16, 1942
  - Item 1: Committee for "Slack" Investigation Report, Publication (Box 4, Folder 49)
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, History of Local 130, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 50)
  April 29, 1949
  - Item 1: History of Local 130, Publication (Box 4, Folder 50)
    April 29, 1949. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, History of Local 131, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: History of Local 131, Publication (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Teper, Lazare, Weinberg, Nathan. Aspects of Industrial Homework in Apparel Trades, 1941; Publication (Box 4, Folder 52)
  July 1941
  - Item 1: Aspects of Industrial Homework in Apparel Trades, Publication (Box 4, Folder 52)
    By Lazare Teper and Nathan Weinberg. July 1941. Item is in English.
- Mitchell, Broadus. Speeches and Articles, Publication (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Speeches and Articles, Publication (Box 4, Folder 53)
    By Mitchell Broadus. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Analysis of Needlework Industry Section of Report of Governor's Committee for the Study of the Effects of the F.L.S.A. on the Industries in Puerto Rico, 1940; Publication (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Analysis of needlework industry section of report of governor's committee for the study of the effects of the F.L.S.A. on the industries in Puerto Rico, Publication (Box 4, Folder 54)
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Material for Use in Cleveland Cloak Industry Wage Negotiations, 1941; Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Material for use in Cleveland cloak industry wage negotiations, Publication (Box 4, Folder 55)
    November 1941. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Social Security Benefits, 1950; Publication (Box 4, Folder 56)
  October 4, 1950
  - Item 1: Social Security Benefits, Publication (Box 4, Folder 56)
    October 4, 1950. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Articles by the Research Department, 1945; Publication (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Articles by the Research Department, Publication (Box 4, Folder 57)
    V.2. Item is in English.
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Articles by the Research Department, 1945; Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Broadus Mitchell, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 2: Organization of the Ladies' Garment Industry in the U.S., Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 3: Status of Homeworkers Under Social Security Act, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 4: Federal And New York State Restrictions On Homework, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 5: Trends in the Women's Apparel Industry: War-time Prosperity, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 6: Minimising Strikes For Union Recognition, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 7: Index of Department Store Sales: January to June 1943, 1944 ,1945, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    Table 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Department Store Stocks: Percentage Change from a Year Ago (Value), Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    Table 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Average Hourly Earnings: Several Branches, Women's Garment Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    Table 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Index of Employment: Several Branches, Women's Garment Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    Table 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Payroll Index, Several Branches, Women's Garment Industry, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    Table 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: For a 65 cents Minimum Testimony, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 13: Statement of Broadus Mitchell, Research Director, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union before House Labor Committee, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    October 26, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Lost Strikes of Yesterday, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 15: Strikes, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 16: Memorandum to: Mr. David Dubinsky, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    October 18, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Administration's Wage-Price Policy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    November 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: 1946 Reduction of Income Taxes, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 19: Union Wage Demands: Wage Demands by ILGWU, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
    August 17, 1945 - November 1, 1945. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Draft of Brief for Impartial Chairman, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 21: U.S. Naturalization Certificates Issues 1910-1940, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 22: U.S. Imigration Statistics: Total Aliens Admitted From All Countries, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Item 23: Conference of National Organizations on America' Commitments for Peace Washington - November 26-27, 1945, Publication (Box 4, Folder 58)
- I.L.G.W.U. Research Department, Data on Puerto Rico, 1940; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  September 1940
  - Item 1: Data on Puerto Rico, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    September 1940. Item is in English.